The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Giant Demon Clan
Ceng Niu killed Li Yuanfeng
and he sealed Xue Yue...
Tian Mu\NHead Elder of the Giant Demon Clan\NPeak Late stage Soul Formation
I fear our Giant Demon Clan won’t escape this calamity.
The Ancestor hasn’t fully possessed his new body
and he hasn’t yet recovered.
Second Elder of the Giant Demon Clan\NPeak Late stage Soul Formation
Fortunately, his seclusion spot is very well hidden.
Ceng Niu will never find it.
Third Elder of the Giant Demon Clan\NPeak Late stage Soul Formation
Whether it's Ceng Niu or Ceng Ma,
Note: "Niu" mean "cow" and "Ma" means "horse"
since he threatens the Ancestor
our Giant Demon Clan will ensure he never finds him !
If Ceng Niu really comes,
that means he is confident…
Although the Ancestor was wrong,
he is the hope of the Giant Demon Clan.
But Ceng Niu…
considers me a real friend.
Alright,
this should work.
Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor,
come out now !
Who are you !?
Ceng Niu.
Ceng Niu, he's the one who won against Red Butterfly !
The number one cultivator under Soul Transformation !
Fellow cultivator Ceng Niu,
why are you looking for the Ancestor ?
To kill him.
The Giant Demon Clan is linked by blood,
we’re not like Xue Yue !
Since you disrespect the Ancestor,
don’t blame us for being ruthless !
I use my status as the Elder of the Giant Demon Clan
to order all clan members
to use everything they have
to kill Ceng Niu !
Kill him !
Seal !
Scram !
Brother Ceng,
please spare them !
Chi Hu…
Brother Ceng…
Do you consider me, Chi Hu, your friend ?
I don't have many friends in my life,
but you, Chi Hu, are one.
The Giant Demon Clan wronged you first
so Brother Ceng’s actions are justified.
But I…
am the Giant Demon Clan’s successor.
If Brother Ceng really sees me as a friend
then I beg you to show mercy
and to leave the clan.
Do you know why I haven't killed anyone yet ?
Chi Hu…
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn’t have spared them.
Brother Ceng…
I…
Why are you wasting words on him !?
Just tell me where the Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor is
and I’ll leave.
So bold !
Arrogant !
If you want to find the Ancestor,
you'll have to get past me first !
Elder,
don’t do it !
Brother Ceng,
the Giant Demon Clan isn’t your enemy.
Where is the Giant Demon Clan Ancestor ?
I might spare him
if he gives back
my celestial sword.
No one knows where the Ancestor is hidden.
Only by activating the Heaven Reaching Formation
can we contact him.
Brother Ceng,
if he returns your sword
will you really leave ?
Three Elders,
by my authority as Junior Clan Leader,
I order you to open the Heaven Reaching Formation !
Giant Demon Clan's Heaven Reaching Formation !
Southern Giant Demon Gate
Western Giant Demon Gate
Northern Giant Demon Gate
Activate !
Ceng Niu always exacts his vengeance.
Since the Ancestor wronged him,
he won’t spare the Ancestor’s life.
He asked for the sword
as a pretext.
Eastern Giant Demon Gate,
activate !
Brother Ceng,
I'm sorry for betraying you.
But the Ancestor is our clan’s hope
As the successor,
I must bear this responsibility !
The Ancestor's old body
could only take 8 blows
from the Heaven Reaching Formation.
You…
can’t possibly survive this.
Chi Hu,
you owe me for what happened
in the Celestial Realm.
I owe you
for your help in Xue Yue.
From now on,
we’re even.
Even...
that's correct...
The two of us
are even !
Chi Hu,
do you really think this Heaven Reaching Formation
can kill me ?
That's the first blow.
Can an outsider really withstand
the formation with his body ?!
Second blow !
What ?!
How can he...
Impossible !
This is impossible !
Even the Ancestor
could only endure 8 blows.
He can’t possibly survive the 12th !
This is the final blow.
Chi Hu,
watch closely !
Giant Demon Clan's Heaven Reaching Formation,
fall !
Fall !
So this is your true strength…
It looks like
even Master underestimated you.
Since none of you will speak,
then I will use your formation to send my voice
far enough so your Ancestor will hear it.
Giant Demon Clan Ancestor,
come for your death !
The fiend !
You really used the vibration of the formation collapse
to send your threat to me ?!
How arrogant !
Once I have finished my possession,
I'll come to kill you immediately !
12 blows...
This is unheard of
in the clan's history.
Giant Demon Clan,
seal !
From now on,
there will be no Nascent Soul or above cultivators !
Without my approval,
you will not get past Core Formation.
This is your punishment.
Master,
let me out !
I’ll fight him to the death !
What did Wang Lin ever do to you
to make you hate him so much ?
He treated me worse than dirt !
He's nothing like you, Master !
Once we kill Wang Lin,
will you let me
see that little sister in your artifact.
Not yet,
once I fully recover,
I’ll let you meet her.
Come out !
You overestimate yourself.
I planned to let you live a few more days
but since you’re eager to die,
I'll deal with you right now !
His possession isn't complete
yet he’s already this powerful ?
If he fully recovers,
his body might rival the strength
a 3-star Ancient God !
How can his body be stronger than mine ?!
I wanted to avoid
using celestial spiritual energy during the possession.
But it looks like
I have no choice !
Slash him to death !
Got it !
Wang Lin,
your Grandpa Xu has come !
Watch as I kill you with your own sword !
I, Xu Liguo, have always been loyal.
Did you think you could control me so easily ?
How did you do it ?!
I had planted a restriction on you !
That's funny because,
you’re no match for my master in restrictions.
Xu Liguo...
Master,
I have done well this time,
be sure to reward me !
The fiend is still the fiend...
Alright.
Really !?
Mountains East of the\NGiant Demon Clan
Bastard,
where are you running to ?!
Blackflame Beast,
appear !
Since he has a Soul Transformation cultivation,
I don't think he played all his cards yet.
I, the 67th-generation Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor,
offer my blood
to summon the ancestral artifact !
Our Ancestor once split heaven and earth with this axe.
He killed two 9-leaf Warriors of the Forsaken Immortal Clan !
Being killed by it
is an honor.
Now go to hell !
I can't withstand this thing !
A perfect opportunity !
Lady Liu Mei,
your opponent
is me.
So what if you're a candidate of Uncle Yunque ?
With your mere Middle stage Soul Formation cultivation,
you can't stop me.
In that case,
please enlighten me.
Come out !
Weren't you going to kill me !?
Sub Soul Flag,
come !
This...
this is the Soul Refining Sect's...
The Billion-Soul Flag ?
Du Tian actually gave it to Wang Lin !?
Lady Liu Mei,
you're no match
for this Soul Flag.
Devour !
The body I was painstakingly taking possession of was destroyed
and my Origin Soul was severely injured again...
Wang Lin...
Bloodline power !
Even if my Origin Soul collapses, I'll drag you down with me !
I'll teleport you in the void
with no way back
and nowhere to go.
You will live in constant fear
until you die miserably !
Formation, activate !
This jade slip
details how to counter the Giant Demon Clan's teleportation spell.
How ?!
I can't stop your bloodline power,
but if I can find my way back,
then it's useless.
An Orientation Formation...
You...
are already dead.
This is impossible...
This is impossible !!!
Zhuque Zi will likely soon learn
of the deaths of the Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor and Li Yuanfeng.
But there are more pressing matters now.
It's nearly been
18 years.
Law of the heavens...
Once again,
I will take Wan'er back from you !
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.